{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162457329","data":{"timestamp":" 947162457329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_alihepa_ghafula_kunukia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162463953","data":{"timestamp":" 947162463953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akitaka_amewaua_mekundu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162471518","data":{"timestamp":" 947162471518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akitaka_amewaua_mekundu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162478151","data":{"timestamp":" 947162478150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162485703","data":{"timestamp":" 947162485703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162492335","data":{"timestamp":" 947162492334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amshike_mwangza_aliitoa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162499888","data":{"timestamp":" 947162499888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amshike_mwangza_aliitoa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162506547","data":{"timestamp":" 947162506547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuepuka_urafiki_tulijua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162513164","data":{"timestamp":" 947162513164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_utavuna_kupanga_aliumwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162519771","data":{"timestamp":" 947162519771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikujua_mvulana_akaosha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162527235","data":{"timestamp":" 947162527235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikujua_mvulana_akaosha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162538079","data":{"timestamp":" 947162538079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikujua_mvulana_akaosha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162544712","data":{"timestamp":" 947162544711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuzirai_waliuza_kuchuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162552207","data":{"timestamp":" 947162552207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuzirai_waliuza_kuchuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162562622","data":{"timestamp":" 947162562621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuzirai_waliuza_kuchuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162568829","data":{"timestamp":" 947162568828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162576292","data":{"timestamp":" 947162576292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162584197","data":{"timestamp":" 947162584196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 90461c13-93e0-4896-aece-03644c122032"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162600504","data":{"timestamp":" 947162600504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 2a61e21e-a2ea-410d-9a76-13a5e1351126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162654215","data":{"timestamp":" 947162654214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 2a61e21e-a2ea-410d-9a76-13a5e1351126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162654523","data":{"timestamp":" 947162654523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 2a61e21e-a2ea-410d-9a76-13a5e1351126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162698434","data":{"timestamp":" 947162698434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_154019"," gameId":" 4a31b0d0-d03a-4931-9b45-fdb3cc6369f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}